avweb.com 2007-12-10

# AVweb Privacy Policy

800 Connecticut Ave, P.O. Box 5656  
Norwalk, CT 06854

Telephone: 203-857-3100  
Email: AVweb Help Desk

* * *

**AVweb Privacy Policy**

**AVweb** is a company dedicated to serving the needs of its customers. In addition, we are deeply committed to protecting your privacy and security when you access **AVweb** or its affiliate owned web sites. 

We believe you have the right to know everything regarding the information we collect about you as you use our web sites...how this information benefits you...and how you can say "no" to the use of any of the information. 

**AVweb** has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to protecting your privacy and security. By using this site, you indicate your acceptance of **AVwebs** ' Online Privacy Policy. 

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible). 

What Information is Collected   
We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, and information provided by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. 

How We Use the Information   
The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes, as well as fulfill customer's orders. 

If you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us or our affiliate companies with information on our products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending us an e-mail at the above address. Please provide us with your exact name and address. 

If you supply us with your email address, you may receive periodic emails other than AVflash from us or our affiliate companies. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address. Please provide us with your exact name and address. 

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online. 

**We do not share postal addresses, email addresses or telephone numbers with other organizations.**

Cookies and How They are Used  
Cookies are tiny pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are set when "Shopping Cart" is in use. This allows us to keep track of your current transaction during the order taking process. We use cookies for Shopping Cart, but we do not store personally identifiable information in your cookie. 

Changes   
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by sending us e-mail at the above address. 

**We Do Not Partner With or Have Special Relationships With Any Ad Server Companies.**

How You Can Access or Correct Information  
Upon request, we provide site visitors with access to transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by e-mailing us at the above address. 

Upon request, we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in all information that we maintain. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address. 

Users are able to access and update portions of their own subscription profile by going to Member Services and clicking on Review/update my AVweb account. There you may update your contact information, email address, password and email subscriptions/preferences. 

Security   
We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. 

**If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above address or phone number.**

_Updated January 23, 2006_
